positivelypositive.com 2017-12-21

# Privacy Policy - Positively Positive!! Positively Positive!!

**Effective Date**

| 

September 1, 2011  
  
**About This Policy**

| 

This policy describes our practices on the websites where it is posted. It also applies to text messages and emails.

This policy does not apply to our use of employee information. It also does not apply to information we collect from you offline.

You agree to the terms in this policy when you use this site.  
  
**Content** **and Information You Share For Publication**

| 

When you share content and other information for publication on the site, for example by submitting any blog, story, photo, audio file, video or other content for publication on the site or by posting a comment on any forum or feedback field, that content and information is publicly available and can be seen, collected and used by others. Such content and information may be associated with you, including your name, photo and video and audio recordings of you. It can be indexed by third party search engines, imported, exported, distributed, and redistributed by us and others through the internet and other media channels without privacy limitations.  
  
**Information We Collect**

| 

**Contact information.** For example, we may collect your name and email address. We may also collect your street address, fax number, or phone number. We may also collect your company name.

**Other information.** If you use our websites, we may collect information about the browser you are using. Our web server may store your IP address and domain. We might track the pages you visit. We might look at what site you came from, or what site you visit when you leave us. We collect this information using tracking tools described in this policy. To control those tools, please read the “Your Choices” section.  
  
**How We Collect Information**

| 

**We collect information directly from you.** For example, if you submit content or other information to us to publish on the site or contact us to ask questions or leave comments. We also collect information if you sign up for our email or text message newsletters.

**We collect information from you passively.** We use tracking tools like browser cookies, flash cookies, and web beacons. To learn more about these tools and how you can control them, please read the “Your Choices” section.

**We collect information that we obtain from third parties.**  
  
**How We Use Information**

| 

**To respond to your questions and requests**.

**To improve our website and update our email lists.** For example, we might use cookies to track new or past website visitors. We may also use tracking tools to see what areas of our site are the most interesting to our visitors.

**To communicate with you about our relationship.**

**For other business purposes.** For example, we may use your email address to contact you about content you submit for publication or to share updates or events.

**To administer our “email a friend” feature.** We may collect others’ email addresses to share information on our site. We do not keep your friends’ information.  
  
**When We Share Information**

| 

**We may share your information for our business purposes and as legally permitted, including** :

**If we think we have to in order to comply with the law**. For example, we will share information to respond to a court order or subpoena. We may also share if a government agency requests. We may also share if an investigatory body requests.

**With third parties who perform services on our behalf**. For example, we share information with vendors. We may also authorize them to collect information on our behalf. Some vendors may be located outside of the United States.

**With our business partners**. If we provide joint products or services, we share information with business partners, who may use your information in a variety of ways, including to communicate offers to you from us and our marketing partners.

**With an acquirer**. We will transfer information if we are acquired by or merged with another company or a portion of our business is sold to another company.

**For other reasons we may describe to you**.  
  
**Third Parties**

| 

We may allow third parties to post advertisements, applications or links on our site so you can access, interact with and use their advertisements, websites and applications through our site. These third parties may place cookies on certain pages of our website. This privacy policy does not cover those third parties or their use of cookies or information you provide to them through interaction with their advertisements, websites or applications.  
  
**Your Choices**

| 

You can opt out of receiving marketing emails or text messages by following the instructions in any marketing emails or text messages you receive. You can also opt-out by sending us an email at info@positivelypositive.com. To request changes to or to review your information, please send us an email at info@positivelypositive.com. You may also email us at info@positivelypositive.com to have your personal information deleted.

You can choose not to provide personal information. However if you don’t provide us with information some website features may not work. You can also choose to configure browser not to accept cookies. If you do so, however, some parts of our website may not work.  
  
**Where We Store Information**

| 

Our sites are generally operated in the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that any information you provide to us may be transferred to the United States. Please also be aware that by using our sites and giving us your information, you consent to such transfer. You also understand that the U.S. may not provide the same level of protections as the laws of your country.  
  
**Children**

| 

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 without verifiable parental consent. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under 13 without such consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If believe that we might have information from a child under 13, please contact us at info@positivelypositive.com.  
  
**Security**

| 

We use industry standard means to protect our website and your information. The Internet is not 100% secure, though. We cannot promise that your use of our site will be completely safe. We encourage you to use caution on the Internet.  
  
**Links**

| 

Our site contains links to third party sites. If you click on one of those links, you will be taken to websites we do not control. This policy does not apply to the information practices of that website. You should read the privacy policy of other websites carefully. We are not responsible for these third party sites.  
  
**Policy Updates**

| 

From time to time we may change our privacy practices. The latest version of this policy will be posted here. Sometimes there may be a material change to this policy that we wish to apply retroactively. If so, we will notify you and obtain your consent to the extent required by law.  
  
**More Questions?**

| 

If you have additional questions you can call us at 424-201-5616, fax us at 866-669-3831, or reach us by email at info@positivelypositive.com. You can write to us at:

Attn: Webmaster, Positively Positive, LLC

2355 Westwood Blvd.

Unit 187

Los Angeles, CA 90064

Please include your email address, name, address and telephone number when you contact us. This helps us handle your request correctly.
